[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which character from the movie Next Friday delivers the following line: Fat bitches need love too, Craig!?", "correct_answer": "Day Day", "incorrect_answers": ["Roach", "Joker", "Uncle Elroy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sometimes sushi is served rolled in nori. What is nori?", "correct_answer": "seaweed", "incorrect_answers": ["meat", "mushroom", "rice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Academy Award did the 2005 movie Star Wars Episode III: Revenge of the Sith win?", "correct_answer": "None of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Best Director", "Best Visual Effects", "Best Makeup"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Black Sea is not connected to the Sea of Azov.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1989 movie Bill  Teds Excellent Adventure, which historical figure do the boys NOT bring back for their history presentation?", "correct_answer": "George Washington", "incorrect_answers": ["Socrates", "Billy the Kid", "Genghis Khan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what geographical region can you find the Paradise Flying Snake, also called Paradise Tree Snake?", "correct_answer": "Asia", "incorrect_answers": ["Central and South America", "North America", "Australia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the subject of study of the science called oology?", "correct_answer": "Eggs", "incorrect_answers": ["Animal reproductive organs", "Bird feathers", "Eels"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happens to criminal Johnny Clay at the end of the 1956 movie The Killing, directed by Stanley Kubrick?", "correct_answer": "He is arrested.", "incorrect_answers": ["He commits suicide.", "He gets killed.", "He gets married."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the optimal body habitus for hot climates is tall and slender, what is one possible condition explaining pygmies?", "correct_answer": "Humidity", "incorrect_answers": ["Ice ages", "Rain", "Low atmospheric preasure"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Restaurant / lounge in The Goonies was only constructed for the movie.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Saturday Night Fever, a movie about the troubled Brooklyn youth, Toni Manero, helped to popularize disco music. In what year did the movie come out?", "correct_answer": "1977", "incorrect_answers": ["1979", "1978", "1976"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who performed the song Highway Junkie for the Black Dog soundtrack?", "correct_answer": "Gary Allan", "incorrect_answers": ["Travis Tritt", "Rambler", "Blake Shelton"]}]